## RAMI DIKA

+(961) 81652310 l ramiDika1999@gmail.com Beirut, Lebanon

## **PROFILE**

Customer Service Professional experienced in account management, project coordination, & sales. Fluent in inventory management, financial analysis, & telecommunication systems. Open to prospects within the Beirut Metropolitan Area, RamiAge 23 embodies a strong work ethic, would be an asset to any team.

## **CORE COMPETENCIES**

- Payroll Cash Management
- Sales Purchase Orders
- Systems Code Modeling
- Inventory Management
- Six Sigma Waste Reduction
- Account Management

- Strategic Marketing Initiatives
- Sales & Business Development

ı

- Business Communications
- Microsoft Office Suite
- Customer Service
- Professional Etiquette

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

CHEF LEBANON PROJECT:

Nov 2022 — currently

Torch Hotel Representative I DOHA, QATAR

- Managing the hospitality needs of high profile clientele at Khalifa Stadium as a customer excellence rep
- Troubleshooting plan concerns to ensure available resources in market, placing orders ahead of schedule based on inventory demand
- Delivering quality customer service to stakeholders of all levels with cold refreshments and warm snack in peripheral view of stadium, restaurant, and hotel area in DT Doha

LAKKIS FARM:

2022 - Oct 2022

Customer service I BAALBACK,LB

- Managing inventory control, order management, and customer service in high volume hospitality business located in the heart of Beqaa, LB
- Conducting product quality reviews to ensure retail process excellence using lean six sigma methodology
- Serving customers with a smile because people deserve smiles with their service

Scanned with CamScanner

#### GRAY MACKENZIE RETAIL HAPPY:

2021 — Oct 2021

FTTEAM MEMBER I HAZMIEH. LB

- Task accomplishments throughout the day include product merchandizing, inventory management, and Just In Time (JIT) delivery
- Strategic product placement throughout store to enhance customer visibility increasing traffic and sales

PHARMACY NISRIN: 1 Oct 2020 -

Jan 2021

PHARMACEUTICAL ASSISTANT I HIZZIN, LB

- Met monthly prescription quotas through the design, sale, and management of programs tailored to each client's needs
- Managed customer contracts (deficiency analysis and sales reports)

CO-OP: | Sep 2020 — Nov 2020

OPEIUTIONAL SUPPORT CO-OP I BAALBEK, LB

- Maintaining daily production of COVID-19 masks to reach target of 100 a day
- Exercised quality assurance protocol and six sigma lean methodologies to prevent manufacturing waste and increase efficiency

## AL-MONA SOCIAL CHARITY:

I June 2019 — Dec 2019

I Jan

LOGISTICS VOLUNTEER I CHMOSTAR, LB

- Initiated nonprofit program funding for produce and financial support work opportunities for the young people to engage more in the social life
- Enabled efficient supply and resource management through efficient teamwork, and working towards a collective goal

TUTOR:

I Jan 2019 — May 2019

PRIVATE TUTOR I BAALBEK, LB

- Prepared daily calendar needed to optimize academic performance In the classroom and upcoming national examinations
- Ensured quality and timely curriculum programming for students grade [7-11]

RANEEM WATER COMPANY:

- Managing 50 water contracts for customers to help Raneem Water Co achieve revenue targets and by delivering quality customer service
- Executive presentations in the form of sales reports that indicate viewing of account volume, forecast of potential usage, and contract expansion
- Overseeing process of water storage, distribution, and bookkeeping of customer communications and sales
- Investigating potential customer market through brand conversion and analyses to improve profitability

# **EDUCATION**

LEBANESE INTERNATIONAL UNIVERSITY (LIU) I BAALBEK, LB

2019-2022

Degree: Bachelors in Telecommunications Engineering (BSc)

SAGES HIGH SCHOOL I BAALBEK, LB

2019

Degree: High School Diploma (HSD)

# **SKILLS/CERTIFICATIONS**

- LYCÉE EMMANUEL BREVET CERTIFICATION
- TERMINAL CERTIFICATE BRANCH LIFE SCIENCES: SAGESSE BAALBEK
- PURCI IASE ORDER PROCESSING
- FINANCIAL MODELING AND FORECASTING
- MlcRosor;-r OFFICE SUITE

# **LANGUAGES**

ARABIC: NATIVE PROFICIENCY

ENGLISH: FULL PROFESSIONAL PROFICIENCY

FRENCH: WORKING PROFICIENCY